<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LearnTurkish</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="ok">Okay</string>
    <string name="okAr">حسنًا</string>
    <string name="changeLanguage">تغيير اللغة</string>
    <string name="whyAds">الإعلانات هي مصدر الدخل الوحيد لمعظم المطورين وصنع التطبيقات يتطلب وقتًا وجهدًا كثيرين، فنحاول أن نستمر في مسيرتنا من خلال هذا.</string>

    <string name="aboutLemonLabAr">    "مختبر الليمون فريق يسعى لنشر تطبيقات تساعد الناس وتسهل حياتهم. \n"
    "نحاول أن نستخدم أحدث الخدمات وأفضل الطرق لإيصال تطبيقاتنا إلى مستوىً منافس. "
    "تطبيقاتنا ترفيهية في غالبها، لكن قد نطوّر بعض التطبيقات التعليمية بين حين وآخر.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText">Privacy Policy of Lemon Lab\n
        \n
        Lemon Lab provides many services including this app.\n
        \n
        This page is used to inform Lemon Lab offers visitors regarding our policies with the collection، use، and
        disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service، the Lemon Lab.\n
        \n
        If you choose to use our Service، then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this
        policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not
        use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.\n
        \n
        The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions، which is accessible
        at Lemon lab، unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n
        \n
        Information Collection and Use\n
        \n
        For a better experience while using our Service، we may require you to provide us with certain personally
        identifiable information، including but not limited to your name، phone number، and postal address. The
        information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.\n
        \n
        Log Data\n
        \n
        We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service، we collect information that your browser sends to us
        that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (\IP\)
        address، browser version، pages of our Service that you visit، the time and date of your visit، the time spent
        on those pages، and other statistics.\n
        \n
        Cookies\n
        \n
        Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent
        to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.\n
        \n
        Our apps uses these cookies to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either
        accept or refuse these cookies، and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse
        our cookies، you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.\n
        \n
        Service Providers\n
        \n
        We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:\n
        \n
        To facilitate our Service;\n
        To provide the Service on our behalf; \n
        To perform Service -related services; \n
        or \n
        To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.\n
        \n
        We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The
        reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However، they are obligated not to disclose or
        use the information for any other purpose.\n
        \n
        Security\n
        \n
        We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information، thus we are striving to use commercially
        acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet، or method of
        electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable، and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n
        \n
        Links to Other Sites\n
        \n
        Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link، you will be directed to that
        site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore، we strongly advise you to review the
        Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over، and assume no responsibility for the content، privacy
        policies، or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n
        \n
        Children’s Privacy\n
        \n
        Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 6. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable
        information from children under 6. In the case we discover that a child under 6 has provided us with personal
        information، we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that
        your child has provided us with personal information، please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary
        actions.\n
        \n
        Changes to This Privacy Policy\n
        \n
        We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus، we advise you to review this page periodically for any
        changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are
        effective immediately، after they are posted on this page.\n
        \n
        Credits\n
        \n
        We used different libraries to make this app. Toasty. Groupie. Daimajia. makeramen. TrueTime. Dexter. Glide. App icon is from icons8.com.\n
        \n
        Contact Us\n
        \n
        If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy، do not hesitate to contact us at
        zaka7024@gmail.com.\n
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicyTextAr">سياسة الخصوصية لدى مختبر الليمون\n
        \n
        يوفر مختبر الليمون عدة خدمات، منها هذا التطبيق.\n
        \n
        هذه الصفحة تحتوي على معلومات لإخبار أي من مستخدمي خدمات مختبر الليمون عن المعلومات الشخصية التي قد نجمعها عند
        استخدامك لإحدى الخدمات.\n
        \n
        إذا استخدمت خدماتنا، فأنت توافق على تحصيل المعلومات واستخدامها حسب هذه السياسة. المعلومات الشخصية التي نجمعها هي
        فقط لتطوير الخدمات التي يوفرها مختبر الليمون ولن نشاركها مع أحد إلا كما يذكر لاحقًا.\n
        \n
        المصطلحات المستخدمة في سياسة الخصوصية لها نفس المعنى في شروط الخدمة التي يمكنك الوصول إليها في مختبر الليمون.
        إلا إذا قيل غير ذلك.\n
        \n
        تجميع المعلومات واستخدامها\n
        \n
        لتجربة أفضل خلال استخدام خدماتنا، قد نطلب منك معلومات تعريفية شخصية تشمل ولا تقتصر على اسمك وهاتفك وعنوانك
        البريدي، وسوف تستخدم للتواصل معك أو التعريف بك.\n
        \n
        بيانات التسجيل\n
        \n
        نود إخبارك أنه في كل مرة تستخدم خدماتنا، فإننا نجمع معلومات يرسلها هاتفك تسمى معلومات التسجيل وقد تشمل بروتوكول
        الانترنت، نسخة المتصفح أو الجهاز، والأماكن التي تزورها في خدماتنا، وقت زيارتك ومدتها وبعض الاحصائيات الأخرى\n
        \n
        ملفات تعريف الارتباط على الإنترنت\n
        \n
        ملفات تعريف الارتباط على الإنترنت هي ملفات صغيرة تحوي بيانات قليلة تستخدم بشكل واسع كمعرف فريد مجهول، ترسل إلى
        المتصفح عبر مواقع الويب وتخزن على جهازك\n
        \n
        تطبيقنا يستخدم ملفات تعريف الارتباط لجمع المعلومات لتطوير خدماتنا، لديك الخيار لرفض أو قبول هذه الملفات والمعرفة
        في حال استخدامنا لها. وفي حال رفضك لهذه الملفات قد لا تستطيع استخدام جزء من خدماتنا.\n
        \n
        موفرو الخدمات\n
        \n
        قد نوظف أفرادًا أو شركات كطرف ثالث للأسباب التالية:\n
        \n
        لتسهيل خدماتنا.\n
        ليوفروا خدماتنا نيابة عنا.\n
        ليقوموا بخدمات متعلقة بالخدمات التي نقدمها.\n
        أو \n
        لمساعدتنا في تحليل الطريقة التي تستخدم فيها خدماتنا.\n
        \n
        نود إخبار مستخدمي خدماتنا أن هذه الشركات لها وصول إلى بياناتهم الشخصية والسبب لتنفيذهم مهمات نحن مختبر الليمون
        طلبناها منهم. وهم مجبرون على أية حال على عدم استخدام تلك البيانات لأي هدف آخر.\n
        \n
        الأمن\n
        \n
        نحن نقدر ثقتك في خدماتنا عند توفيرك للمعلومات لذلك نحن نستخدم طرقًا مقبولة لحمايتها لكن يجب أن تتذكر أنه ليس
        هناك طريقة على الانترنت أو إلكترونية آمنة كليًا.\n
        \n
        روابط لمواقع أخرى\n
        \n
        قد تحتوي خدماتنا روابط لمواقع أخرى، لذا فإننا ننصح بمراجعة سياسة الخصوصية لتلك المواقع لأننا لسنا مسؤولين عن أي
        انتهاك لأن تلك المواقع ليست من مختبر الليمون\n
        \n
        خصوصية الأطفال\n
        \n
        خدماتنا لا تستقبل أي طفل تحت الست سنوات، إذا لاحظنا أن طفلًا تحت الست سنوات قد أعطى معلومات شخصية فإننا نحذفها
        فور وصولها. إذا كنت والدًا أو ولي أمر طفل تعتقد أنه استخدم خدماتنا، تواصل معنا وسنقوم بالإجراءات الضرورية.\n
        \n
        التغييرات على سياسة الخصوصية\n
        \n
        \nقد نقوم بتغيير سياسة الخصوصية لدينا في أي وقت، لذا ينصح بالاطلاع على هذه الصفحة دوريًا. علمًا بأننا سنعلمك في
        حال التغيير، والتغييرات ستطبق فور نشرها هنا.
        \n
        \n
        تواصل معنا \n
        \n
        إذا كان لديك أي أسئلة أو اقتراحات أو استفسارات حول سياسة الخصوصية، لا تتردد في مراسلتنا على zaka7024@gmail.com\n
    </string>

    <string name="credits">
        akexorcist: Android-RoundCornerProgressBar
        \n\n
        airbnb: lottie-android
        \n\n
        traex: RippleEffect
        \n\n
        hdodenhof: CircleImageView
        \n\n
        square: picasso
        \n\n
        daimajia: AndroidViewAnimations
        \n\n
        Websites:
        turkishlearneasy.blogspot.com/2011/09/blog-post_3290.html?m=1
        \n
        duroos.org/turkish_lesson1.php
    </string>

</resources>
